# NDAYISHIMIYE Serge Regis

- **\** 0786285968
- ## https://www.linkedin.com/in/ndayishimiye-serge-regis-363b481a3/
- Kicukiro
- Rwanda
- https://sergeregis.netlify.app/
- https://github.com/SergeRegis



#### **₽≡** PROFILE

I am a seasoned IT professional with over 5 years of experience in providing technical solutions to organizational challenges. My expertise covers a wide range of IT activities, such as software development, infrastructure installation, system management, and database administration. I have a deep understanding of English, IT concepts, and best practices. I am also a strong communicator and excel in complex problem-solving. My background and abilities make me a valuable asset in any organization.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Front-end developer At Payngtone, Payngtone

• Demonstrated expertise in HTML5, CSS3, object-orientated JavaScript, and large JavaScript applications.

- Coordinated usability testing and corrective action of bugs.
- Designed and implemented website interface for mobile, desktop, and tablets.
- Proficient in JavaScript frameworks such as Angular, React, Ember, and Backbone.
- Specialized in front-end framework construction using Reactjs.
- Contributed to back-end experience and collaborated on APIs.
- Developed and integrated payment processing features onto eCommerce websites.

#### IT Development Intern At Isiine Innovative center,

Isiine Innovative Center

- Managing the installation, maintenance, and documentation of IT systems
- Leading the development and implementation of successful IT strategies and procedures
- Designing, implementing, and testing various web-based applications and features

10/2022 - 12/2022

Kicukiro, Rwanda

06/2022 - 09/2022

Kigali, Rwanda

- Troubleshooting hardware and software issues in a timely manner
- Developing custom scripts and programs to automate certain processes
- Coordinating with vendors to ensure efficient procurement processes
- Providing support and training to end users on IT systems and operations

### (P) SKILLS

Well-versed in programming languages such as C, Flutter, and Java

EBM , Taxation & E-Procurement

Proficient in web development tools and technologies such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript • • • •

Experienced in designing,

building, and maintaining

databases

Knowledgeable in systems analysis, problem-solving, and information security Excellent communication and interpersonal skills

• • • • •

#### **EDUCATION**

**Advanced DIploma,** Integrated Polytechnic Regional College Kigali Information Technology

09/2018 – 12/2022 Kicukiro, Rwanda

**A-Levels,** ETO Nyamata Computer Electronics 01/2015 - 10/2018

O-Levels, College Don Bosco de Rushaki

01/2012 - 10/2014

Byumba, Rwanda

Nyamata, Rwanda

## **CERTIFICATES**

- Achieved certification In English Course at Alison English Bootcamp
- Achieved certification In Javascript Course Hackerank Bootcamp.
- Achieved certification In Frontend development at FreeCodeCamp Bootcamp.

 EMB , Taxation and Eprocurement certificate

## LANGUAGES

• English

• Kinyarwanda

## **≈** REFERENCES

**Isiine phionah**, CEO At Isiine isiinephionah@gmail.com, 0788809593

**Sheja Eddy**, Chief Technology Officer at Payingtone, payingtone 0784141587

**Nshimiyimana Eugene**, *Lawyer*, NSE Law Chamber 0788352940

## **DECLARATION**

I declare on my honor that the information provided above is in accordance with reality.

NDAYISHIMIYE Serge Regis

Kigali, 16/02/2023